pharmapacks.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy

_Effective Date: 04/17/2015_

This privacy policy applies to **[http://www.pharmapacks.com](http://www.pharmapacks.com/) **owned and operated by Pharmapacks LLC. This privacy policy describes how Pharmapacks LLC collects and uses the personally identifiable information you provide on our web site: [**http://www.pharmapacks.com**](http://www.pharmapacks.com/).  It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personally identifiable information and how you can access and update this information.

Pharmapacks LLC. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with **[TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) **including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personally [identifiable](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [**privacy@pharmapacks.com**](mailto:privacy@pharmapacks.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [**TRUSTe here**](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). The TRUSTe program and this privacy policy covers only information that is collected through [**www.pharmapacks.com**](http://www.pharmapacks.com/)and does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will share your personally identifiable information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. 

**Personally Identifiable Information We Collect**

We collect personally identifiable information in different ways, for different reasons. General info (e.g. name, address, e-mail, phone number) and billing info (such as credit card information) are collected for the purpose of order fulfillment and if need be, follow up to ensure a satisfactory customer experience. Information associated with a state or federally issued ID is collected and stored to monitor the sale (and amount) of Ephederine, Pseudoephederine and Phenylpropanolamine to an individual customer in a specific time frame. Personal health conditions and/or allergies of a specific customer are gathered to ensure a proper drug therapy utilization review.

**How We Use Your Personally Identifiable Information**

The site uses the information collected to bill you for, and deliver ordered products in the amount of time expected by the customer, per our shipping terms. We will also use the information we collect to contact you in the event there is an issue with your order, or if you request information or support from us. Non-personally-identifying information is used to track a product's sales frequency and for consideration regarding incentives, and status on Pharmapacks, LLC website.

Collection of 3rd party PII: You may also provide personally identifiable information about other people, such as their name and physical address. This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided.

**Newsletters**

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. You may unsubscribe from these communications at any time by following the instruction contained within each of the communications you receive.

**Service-related Announcements**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

**Gift Certificates**

If you choose to use our gift certificate service to purchase a gift certificate for a friend on our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email providing him or her with the gift certificate. Pharmapacks, LLC stores this information for the purpose(s) of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our program.

Your friend may contact us at [**privacy@pharmapacks.com**](mailto:privacy@pharmapacks.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Service Providers**

We use other third parties such as a payment gateway company to bill you for goods and services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf, and a hosting company to provide you with our community forums. We use Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding your order.These companies are authorized to use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to provide these services to us. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personally identifiableinformation as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Business Transitions**

In the event Pharmapacks, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to any such change in ownership or control of your personally identifiable information, as well as choices you have regarding your personally identifiable information.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [**customercare@pharmapacks.com**](mailto:customercare@pharmapacks.com). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Security**

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Tracking Technologies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Pharmapacks LLC and our partners, Google Adwords, Bing, Google Analytics or service providers, Veinteractive. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies to maintain user authentication, cart and checkout _._ Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.  

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate, including site usage, traffic sources, visitor segmentation by browser and geography, and volume statistics, to improve customer experience and to target outreach efforts more effectively.

**Local Storage Objects (HTML5)**

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) used by social sharing platform AddThis to store the persistent user's configuration of the AddThis sharing widget. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

**Behavioral Targeting/ Re-Targeting**

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [**Here**](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) .  Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Links to Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Pharmapacks, LLC. Please be aware that we, Pharmapacks, LLC, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policy of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this Web site.

**Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Customer Reviews**

We post customer reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. When a customer chooses to post a review of a product, we may ask for their information such as name and email address. If you would like to request to have your product review removed from our site you may do so my contacting us at [**customercare@pharmapacks.com**](mailto:customercare@pharmapacks.com).

**Public Forums**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our public forum, contact us at [**forums@pharmapacks.com**](mailto:forums@pharmapacks.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should contact us at [**privacy@pharmapacks.com**](mailto:privacy@pharmapacks.com) or via postal mail at:

Pharmapacks, LLC 110-25 110th Avenue, College Point NY 11356
